01 00000 1. The IT department is reporting that a company web server is receiving an abnormally high number o
02 00263 2. What causes a buffer overflow? ? launching a security countermeasure to mitigate a Trojan horse ?
03 00721 3. Which objective of secure communications is achieved by encrypting data? ? authentication ? avail
04 01072 4. What type of malware has the primary objective of spreading across the network? ? worm ? virus ? 
05 01194 5. What commonly motivates cybercriminals to attack networks as compared to hactivists or state-spon
06 01569 6. Which type of hacker is motivated to protest against political and social issues? ? hacktivist ? 
07 01851 7. What is a ping sweep? ? a query and response protocol that identifies information about a domain,
08 02656 8. In what type of attack is a cybercriminal attempting to prevent legitimate users from accessing n
09 02965 9. Which requirement of secure communications is ensured by the implementation of MD5 or SHA hash ge
10 03515 10. If an asymmetric algorithm uses a public key to encrypt data, what is used to decrypt it? ? a di
11 03997 11. Refer to the exhibit. Which two ACLs would permit only the two LAN networks attached to R1 to ac
12 04775 12. Which two packet filters could a network administrator use on an IPv4 extended ACL? (Choose two.
13 05174 13. What type of ACL offers greater flexibility and control over network access? ? numbered standard
14 05458 14. What is the quickest way to remove a single ACE from a named ACL? ? Use the no keyword and the s
15 05970 15. Refer to the exhibit. A network administrator is configuring a standard IPv4 ACL. What is the ef
16 06579 16. Refer to the exhibit. A network administrator has configured ACL 9 as shown. Users on the 172.31
17 07492 17. A network administrator needs to configure a standard ACL so that only the workstation of the ad
18 08280 18. Refer to the exhibit. Which command would be used in a standard ACL to allow only devices on the
19 08880 19. A network administrator is writing a standard ACL that will deny any traffic from the 172.16.0.0
20 09593 20. Refer to the exhibit. An ACL was configured on R1 with the intention of denying traffic from sub
24 09734 24. All other traffic into subnet 172.16.3.0/24 should be permitted. This standard ACL was then appl
21 10540 21. Refer to the exhibit. A network administrator needs to add an ACE to the TRAFFIC-CONTROL ACL tha
20 10691 20. Which ACE will meet this requirement? ? 30 deny 172.23.16.0 0.0.15.255 ? 15 deny 172.23.16.0 0.0
22 11371 22. Refer to the exhibit. A network administrator configures an ACL on the router. Which statement d
23 12187 23. Refer to the exhibit. What can be determined from this output? ? The ACL is missing the deny ip 
24 13170 24. Refer to the exhibit. A network administrator wants to permit only host 192.168.1.1 /24 to be ab
24 13307 24. Which three commands will achieve this using best ACL placement practices? (Choose three.) ? R2(
25 14070 25. Consider the following access list. access-list 100 permit ip host 192.168.10.1 any access-list 
26 15373 26. Refer to the exhibit. The named ACL ?Managers? already exists on the router. What will happen wh
27 15830 27. In which TCP attack is the cybercriminal attempting to overwhelm a target host with half-open TC
28 16381 28. Which protocol is attacked when a cybercriminal provides an invalid gateway in order to create a
29 16942 29. Refer to the exhibit. An administrator has configured a standard ACL on R1 and applied it to int
30 17634 30. Refer to the exhibit. The Gigabit interfaces on both routers have been configured with subinterf
12 17858 12. PCs on VLAN 20 should print to the printers on VLAN 22. What interface and in what direction sho
22 17914 22. What interface and in what direction should you place a standard ACL that allows printing to P1 
31 18816 31. Which statement describes a characteristic of standard IPv4 ACLs? ? They are configured in the i
32 19459 32. What is considered a best practice when configuring ACLs on vty lines? ? Place identical restric
33 19737 33. Refer to the exhibit. An administrator first configured an extended ACL as shown by the output o
34 20650 34. Which set of access control entries would allow all users on the 192.168.10.0/24 network to acce
35 21632 35. What is the term used to describe a mechanism that takes advantage of a vulnerability? ? mitigat
36 21771 36. Refer to the exhibit. The network administrator has an IP address of 192.168.11.10 and needs acc
01 21886 1. What is the best ACL type and placement to use in this situation? ? extended ACL outbound on R2 W
37 22774 37. A technician is tasked with using ACLs to secure a router. When would the technician use the any
38 23100 38. Which statement accurately characterizes the evolution of threats to network security? ? Interne
39 23726 39. A user receives a phone call from a person who claims to represent IT services and then asks tha
40 24310 40. In what way are zombies used in security attacks? ? They target specific individuals to gain cor
41 24816 41. Which attack involves threat actors positioning themselves between a source and destination with
42 25287 42. Which two keywords can be used in an access control list to replace a wildcard mask or address a
43 25817 43. Which statement describes a difference between the operation of inbound and outbound ACLs? ? Inb
44 26775 44. What effect would the Router1(config-ext-nacl)# permit tcp 172.16.4.0 0.0.0.255 any eq www comma
45 27217 45. Which ACE will permit a packet that originates from any network and is destined for a web server
46 27558 46. Refer to the exhibit. A new network policy requires an ACL denying FTP and Telnet access to a Co
47 28331 47. A technician is tasked with using ACLs to secure a router. When would the technician use the acc
48 28636 48. What is the term used to describe the same pre-shared key or secret key, known by both the sende
49 28847 49. Refer to the exhibit. Internet privileges for an employee have been revoked because of abuse but
50 29968 50. Refer to the exhibit. The student on the H1 computer continues to launch an extended ping with e
01 30596 1. Explanation: This access list must be an extended ACL in order to filter on specific source and d
01 30804 1. Traffic from H1 travels into the switch, then out of the switch into the R1 Gi0/0 interface. This
51 31091 51. A technician is tasked with using ACLs to secure a router. When would the technician use the ?ip
52 31420 52. In which type of attack is falsified information used to redirect users to malicious Internet si
53 31763 53. What is a feature of an IPS? ? It can stop malicious packets. ? It is deployed in offline mode. 
54 32153 54. What is the term used to describe a potential danger to a company?s assets, data, or network fun
55 32308 55. Refer to the exhibit. Network 192.168.30.0/24 contains all of the company servers. Policy dictat
56 33386 56. What does the CLI prompt change to after entering the command ip access-list standard aaa from g
57 33626 57. Refer to the exhibit. Many employees are wasting company time accessing social media on their wo
58 34056 58. A technician is tasked with using ACLs to secure a router. When would the technician use the 40 
59 34379 59. What is the best description of Trojan horse malware? ? It is malware that can only be distribut
60 34680 60. What wild card mask will match networks 172.16.0.0 through 172.19.0.0? ? 0.0.3.255 ? 0.252.255.2
60 35057 60. What is the term used to describe gray hat hackers who publicly protest organizations or governm
61 35332 61. Refer to the exhibit. The company has provided IP phones to employees on the 192.168.10.0/24 net
62 36377 62. A technician is tasked with using ACLs to secure a router. When would the technician use the no 
63 36686 63. What is the term used to describe unethical criminals who compromise computer and network securi
64 36908 64. What is the term used to describe a guarantee that the message is not a forgery and does actuall
65 37106 65. A technician is tasked with using ACLs to secure a router. When would the technician use the ip 
66 37433 66. A technician is tasked with using ACLs to secure a router. When would the technician use the rem
67 37792 67. Refer to the exhibit. The company CEO demands that one ACL be created to permit email traffic to
68 38201 68. A technician is tasked with using ACLs to secure a router. When would the technician use the est
69 38543 69. A technician is tasked with using ACLs to secure a router. When would the technician use the den
70 38887 70. Refer to the exhibit. Only authorized remote users are allowed remote access to the company serv
71 39285 71. Refer to the exhibit. Employees on 192.168.11.0/24 work on critically sensitive information and 
72 39636 72. A technician is tasked with using ACLs to secure a router. When would the technician use the hos
73 39963 73. What commonly motivates cybercriminals to attack networks as compared to hacktivists or state-sp
count 82
